const quiz1data = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "__ want to go to the beach tomorrow.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "I", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "Me", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: '"I" is a subject pronoun. We use subject pronouns as the subject of a verb. Subjects usually appear before the verb.'
   },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "I saw __ in town yesterday.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "she", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "her", isCorrect: true}
      ],
      help: '"her" is an object pronoun. We use object pronouns as the object of a verb. Objects normally follow the verb. '
   },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "Jessica and __ went to the cinema last Saturday.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "I", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "me", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'A good way to check which one is the correct answer is to remove "Jessica" at the beginning of the sentence and re-read it to see if it sounds right.'
   },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "Sally is waiting for __.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "I", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "me", isCorrect: true}
      ],
      help: '"me" is an object pronoun. We use object pronouns after prepositions.'
   },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "If you ask James and __, basketball is better than football.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "me", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "I", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'A good way to check which one is the correct answer is to remove the other people from the sentence and re-read it to see if it sounds right.'
   },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "-Is that John's car? -No, it's __.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "mine", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "my", isCorrect: false}
      ],
      help:'We use possessive pronouns to avoid repeating words. '
   },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "He lived by __ in an enormous house.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "him", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "himself", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'We use reflexive pronouns with the preposition by.'
   },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "I saw Steve __ a concert on Saturday.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "in", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "on", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "to", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "at", isCorrect: true},
      ]
   },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "Sandra is a friend of __.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "me", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "mine", isCorrect: true}
      ],
      help: 'We can use possessive pronouns after of.'
   },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "I saw __ in the mirror.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "myself", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "me", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use a reflexive pronoun when we want to refer back to the subject of the sentence or clause.'
   },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "There was a robbery ___ the supermarket.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "on", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "in", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "at", isCorrect: true},
      ]
   },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "Between you and __, I think Gabby cheated.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "me", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "I", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'The word "between" is a preposition. That means it requires an object pronoun.'
   },
  ]
export default quiz1data
